


// important questions 
const Home: React.FC = () => {
  const questions: Question[] = [
    { question: 'An E.E.G is one of the main tests to help diagnose heart failure', answer: false },
    {question:'TMS or transcranial magnetic stimulation  manipulates brain activity by inducing electrical activity in a specific brain areas', answer: true},
    {question:'The biosignals detected by EEG have been shown to represent the postsynaptic potentials of pyramidal neurons in the monocortex ', answer: false},
    {question:'Postsynaptic potentials are changes in membrane potential that move the cell away from its resting state.',answer :true},
    {question:'The neocortex is a set of layers of the mammalian cerebral cortex involved in higher-order brain functions such as sensory perception, cognition', answer:true},
    {question :' the percentage allocortex.takes in the brain is 27% ',answer: false},
    {question :'postsynaptic potentials : it is the difference between electric potential between the interior and exterior of biological cells' , answer:true},
    {question:'An action potential occurs when the membrane potential of a specific cell rapidly rises and falls', answer:true},
    {question :'mitochondria organelle found in the cytoplasm of almost all prokaryotic cells ,the primary function of which is to generate large quantities of energy in the form of ATP',answer: false},
    {question :'Stem cells are found in almost all tissues of the body. And they are needed for the maintenance of tissue as well as for repair after injury.',  answer:true}
    
  ]


